100 Most Subscribed YouTube Channels - Bangladesh
@zanzamin - Zan Zamin
Subscribers: 4.1M | Views: 2.4B | Videos: 399
Joined youtube at: 16 July 2017
@ssfcjunior - SS Food Challenge Junior
Subscribers: 4.1M | Views: 3.5B | Videos: 1.9K
Joined youtube at: 23 October 2023
@niloykhansagor1 - Niloy Khan Sagor
Subscribers: 4.1M | Views: 1.0B | Videos: 203
Joined youtube at: 22 November 2018
@maasranganewsbd - Maasranga News
Subscribers: 4.1M | Views: 1.2B | Videos: 42.7K
Joined youtube at: 12 February 2017
@উততরধিকরী - উত্তরাধিকারী
Subscribers: 4.2M | Views: 313.1M | Videos: 785
Joined youtube at: 09 August 2017
@kikenokivabe - Ki Keno Kivabe
Subscribers: 4.2M | Views: 350.9M | Videos: 742
Joined youtube at: 16 October 2017
@mhrbanglawazz - MHR BANGLA WAZ
Subscribers: 4.2M | Views: 570.7M | Videos: 1.5K
Joined youtube at: 22 November 2015
@roxmangaming01 - ROXMAN GAMING
Subscribers: 4.3M | Views: 311.8M | Videos: 507
Joined youtube at: 20 March 2021
@shohagdrz - SHOHAG DRz
Subscribers: 4.3M | Views: 1.6B | Videos: 2.4K
Joined youtube at: 03 January 2022
@gseriesmoviesongs2507 - G Series Movie Songs
Subscribers: 4.3M | Views: 1.5B | Videos: 829
Joined youtube at: 13 September 2017
@maasrangatvofficial - Maasranga TV Official
Subscribers: 4.3M | Views: 1.1B | Videos: 7.8K
Joined youtube at: 30 May 2017
@alheraislamiccenter - AL HERA ISLAMIC CENTER
Subscribers: 4.3M | Views: 830.2M | Videos: 8.5K
Joined youtube at: 27 June 2015
@gangleder-e6d - 1xbet Melbet Tips
Subscribers: 4.3M | Views: 146.5K | Videos: 23
Joined youtube at: 29 January 2023
@annafee_official - An Nafee
Subscribers: 4.3M | Views: 794.4M | Videos: 426
Joined youtube at: 25 May 2018
@thebvnews24 - BVNEWS24
Subscribers: 4.3M | Views: 1.9B | Videos: 38.9K
Joined youtube at: 27 August 2019
@shohagkhandokar9262 - shohag khandokar
Subscribers: 4.4M | Views: 197.5M | Videos: 520
Joined youtube at: 04 September 2018
@boishakhitvbd - Boishakhi TV
Subscribers: 4.4M | Views: 861.3M | Videos: 10.9K
Joined youtube at: 15 December 2015
@bossusmanofficial - BOSS  USMAN
Subscribers: 4.4M | Views: 89.4M | Videos: 110
Joined youtube at: 30 June 2020
@maasrangakids - Maasranga Kids
Subscribers: 4.4M | Views: 3.2B | Videos: 5.1K
Joined youtube at: 05 April 2022
@alamin_akash - Alamin Akash
Subscribers: 4.5M | Views: 1.1B | Videos: 1.0K
Joined youtube at: 14 November 2022
@cinemawalabd - CINEMAWALA
Subscribers: 4.5M | Views: 1.1B | Videos: 460
Joined youtube at: 27 September 2017
@itzkabbo - Itz Kabbo
Subscribers: 4.5M | Views: 827.2M | Videos: 1.9K
Joined youtube at: 30 July 2017
@masudinfobd - Masudinfobd
Subscribers: 4.6M | Views: 1.7B | Videos: 1.7K
Joined youtube at: 20 February 2023
@tigermediaofficial - Tiger Media
Subscribers: 4.6M | Views: 1.7B | Videos: 793
Joined youtube at: 05 May 2014
@rtvmusic - Rtv Music
Subscribers: 4.6M | Views: 1.2B | Videos: 1.4K
Joined youtube at: 13 June 2017
@islamicwazbograofficial - Islamic Waz Bogra
Subscribers: 4.6M | Views: 1.1B | Videos: 6.0K
Joined youtube at: 27 November 2016
@aroundmebd - AroundMeBD
Subscribers: 4.6M | Views: 1.6B | Videos: 2.8K
Joined youtube at: 01 September 2016
@cryptovanguardx - CRYPTO VANGUARD
Subscribers: 4.6M | Views: 179.3M | Videos: 52
Joined youtube at: 20 June 2021
@mytvbangla - mytv Bangladesh
Subscribers: 4.6M | Views: 985.3M | Videos: 35.9K
Joined youtube at: 07 July 2014
@akibislamictv - Akib Islamic TV
Subscribers: 4.7M | Views: 1.6B | Videos: 1.3K
Joined youtube at: 09 December 2019
@sultan_entertainment - Sultan Entertainment
Subscribers: 4.7M | Views: 1.9B | Videos: 427
Joined youtube at: 03 April 2021
@chanderburi - চাঁদের বুড়ি
Subscribers: 4.7M | Views: 1.4B | Videos: 1.4K
Joined youtube at: 06 July 2019
@mas-mediainfo - Mas Media Info
Subscribers: 4.7M | Views: 4.6B | Videos: 822
Joined youtube at: 20 May 2024
@sbcinemahall - SB Cinema Hall
Subscribers: 4.8M | Views: 1.6B | Videos: 2.1K
Joined youtube at: 04 March 2020
@islamerrasta - Islamer Rasta
Subscribers: 5.0M | Views: 811.8M | Videos: 2.4K
Joined youtube at: 05 February 2017
@ruposhibanglatvnews - Ruposhi Bangla Tv
Subscribers: 5.0M | Views: 1.4B | Videos: 8.8K
Joined youtube at: 20 December 2016
@fagunav - Fagun Audio Vision
Subscribers: 5.0M | Views: 1.3B | Videos: 2.1K
Joined youtube at: 05 May 2014
@nahid_hasanj - Nahid Hasan Vlogs
Subscribers: 5.1M | Views: 3.2B | Videos: 933
Joined youtube at: 20 March 2022
@jibonerkotha - Jiboner Kotha
Subscribers: 5.1M | Views: 1.0B | Videos: 2.7K
Joined youtube at: 21 May 2016
@onemanarmy360 - ONE MAN ARMY
Subscribers: 5.2M | Views: 591.9M | Videos: 330
Joined youtube at: 21 November 2022
@dhkobirkhanofficial - Dh kobir khan
Subscribers: 5.3M | Views: 1.6B | Videos: 635
Joined youtube at: 09 March 2016
@rituhossain - Ritu Hossain
Subscribers: 5.3M | Views: 1.6B | Videos: 446
Joined youtube at: 01 April 2016
@prothomalo - Prothom Alo
Subscribers: 5.4M | Views: 1.4B | Videos: 32.2K
Joined youtube at: 30 October 2014
@rsyasinraj251 - Rs Yasin Raj
Subscribers: 5.4M | Views: 2.6B | Videos: 1.1K
Joined youtube at: 13 March 2022
@nabil0 - NABIL
Subscribers: 5.5M | Views: 407.4M | Videos: 583
Joined youtube at: 20 December 2021
@hello24prankking - Hello 24
Subscribers: 5.6M | Views: 2.2B | Videos: 906
Joined youtube at: 12 January 2021
@tsportsbd - T Sports
Subscribers: 5.6M | Views: 1.2B | Videos: 22.5K
Joined youtube at: 02 October 2020
@nusratjahanontoraa - Nusrat Jahan Ontora
Subscribers: 5.8M | Views: 1.8B | Videos: 835
Joined youtube at: 26 April 2018
@eaglemusiccity - Eagle Music City
Subscribers: 5.9M | Views: 1.2B | Videos: 436
Joined youtube at: 05 December 2017
@bbcbangla - BBC News বাংলা
Subscribers: 6.0M | Views: 1.3B | Videos: 7.7K
Joined youtube at: 13 May 2015
@banglavisiondrama - Banglavision DRAMA
Subscribers: 6.0M | Views: 2.2B | Videos: 4.7K
Joined youtube at: 04 December 2013
@deshtvnews - Desh TV News
Subscribers: 6.0M | Views: 3.5B | Videos: 87.0K
Joined youtube at: 14 June 2020
@bongobdmovies - Bongo Movies
Subscribers: 6.1M | Views: 777.6M | Videos: 853
Joined youtube at: 26 November 2015
@anupammovies - Anupam Movies
Subscribers: 6.1M | Views: 1.8B | Videos: 1.3K
Joined youtube at: 05 February 2018
@channelinews - Channel i News
Subscribers: 6.2M | Views: 1.9B | Videos: 82.8K
Joined youtube at: 17 April 2015
@mrtripler - Mr. Triple R
Subscribers: 6.3M | Views: 1.3B | Videos: 2.3K
Joined youtube at: 24 December 2018
@muktaeasydrawing - Mukta easy drawing
Subscribers: 6.3M | Views: 2.7B | Videos: 1.7K
Joined youtube at: 25 November 2016
@juwelchowdhuryofficial - Juwel Chowdhury
Subscribers: 6.5M | Views: 3.6B | Videos: 1.7K
Joined youtube at: 24 February 2021
@soundtek - Soundtek
Subscribers: 6.6M | Views: 1.9B | Videos: 3.7K
Joined youtube at: 31 March 2016
@news24tv - NEWS24
Subscribers: 6.6M | Views: 2.3B | Videos: 141.4K
Joined youtube at: 27 July 2016
@bayazid0007 - Baized Mahmud
Subscribers: 6.7M | Views: 3.6B | Videos: 1.0K
Joined youtube at: 30 September 2020
@funnyfictions - Funny Fictions
Subscribers: 6.9M | Views: 1.3B | Videos: 585
Joined youtube at: 26 January 2022
@gseriesbanglanatoktelefilm - G Series Bangla Natok
Subscribers: 7.1M | Views: 1.7B | Videos: 1.5K
Joined youtube at: 16 February 2016
@againfoysal2.0 - AGAIN FOYSAl
Subscribers: 7.1M | Views: 833.9M | Videos: 1.1K
Joined youtube at: 25 February 2017
@atnnewsltd - ATN News
Subscribers: 7.2M | Views: 3.2B | Videos: 112.2K
Joined youtube at: 20 September 2013
@advancesearchisback - Advance Search is Back
Subscribers: 7.2M | Views: 2.2B | Videos: 993
Joined youtube at: 26 May 2023
@mukta_art_craft - Mukta Art & Craft
Subscribers: 7.3M | Views: 2.9B | Videos: 1.9K
Joined youtube at: 04 December 2017
@cdchoicedrama - CD CHOICE Drama
Subscribers: 7.3M | Views: 2.4B | Videos: 2.4K
Joined youtube at: 25 October 2016
@ntvlatestnews - NTV News
Subscribers: 7.3M | Views: 2.3B | Videos: 96.0K
Joined youtube at: 29 October 2015
@eaglebanglanatokofficial - Eagle Bangla Natok
Subscribers: 7.5M | Views: 2.0B | Videos: 2.1K
Joined youtube at: 24 August 2015
@ntvnatok - NTV Natok
Subscribers: 7.7M | Views: 2.9B | Videos: 20.7K
Joined youtube at: 29 October 2015
@mrrupaiy - MR RUPAI YT
Subscribers: 8.1M | Views: 959.0M | Videos: 647
Joined youtube at: 30 October 2021
@rtvdrama - Rtv Drama
Subscribers: 8.2M | Views: 2.6B | Videos: 6.6K
Joined youtube at: 04 April 2017
@cdchoicelabel - CD Choice
Subscribers: 8.2M | Views: 2.5B | Videos: 2.0K
Joined youtube at: 18 January 2014
@dhrubatv - Dhruba TV
Subscribers: 8.3M | Views: 2.7B | Videos: 4.5K
Joined youtube at: 06 August 2016
@atnbanglanews - ATN Bangla News
Subscribers: 8.3M | Views: 3.3B | Videos: 70.3K
Joined youtube at: 31 January 2018
@banglavisionnews - BanglaVision NEWS
Subscribers: 8.5M | Views: 3.3B | Videos: 61.6K
Joined youtube at: 18 January 2017
@sangeetamusicbd - Sangeeta Music
Subscribers: 8.6M | Views: 3.1B | Videos: 3.2K
Joined youtube at: 17 February 2015
@somoytvbulletin - SOMOY TV Bulletin
Subscribers: 8.8M | Views: 3.3B | Videos: 80.9K
Joined youtube at: 12 July 2017
@alorpothmultimedia - আলোর পথ
Subscribers: 8.9M | Views: 1.5B | Videos: 1.8K
Joined youtube at: 05 July 2016
@eaglepremierstation - Eagle Premier Station
Subscribers: 8.9M | Views: 2.6B | Videos: 2.1K
Joined youtube at: 26 September 2014
@channelionline - Channel i Tv
Subscribers: 9.0M | Views: 2.9B | Videos: 10.9K
Joined youtube at: 10 February 2015
@prankkingbd - Prank King Entertainment
Subscribers: 9.1M | Views: 2.3B | Videos: 308
Joined youtube at: 27 August 2013
@gseriesbanglamovies - G Series Bangla Movies
Subscribers: 9.3M | Views: 2.4B | Videos: 468
Joined youtube at: 16 February 2016
@rosetv24original - Rose Tv24
Subscribers: 9.9M | Views: 2.0B | Videos: 5.8K
Joined youtube at: 04 April 2017
@holytunebdofficial - Holy Tune
Subscribers: 10.0M | Views: 2.5B | Videos: 1.2K
Joined youtube at: 14 January 2011
@cmv - CMV
Subscribers: 10.0M | Views: 3.3B | Videos: 341
Joined youtube at: 08 January 2016
@eaglemusicvideostation - Eagle Music Video Station
Subscribers: 10.1M | Views: 2.6B | Videos: 748
Joined youtube at: 25 June 2016
@kingisback234 - KinG Is BacK
Subscribers: 10.2M | Views: 851.2M | Videos: 695
Joined youtube at: 26 December 2017
@rtvnews - Rtv News
Subscribers: 10.3M | Views: 5.3B | Videos: 157.0K
Joined youtube at: 20 September 2016
@bongo-bd - Bongo
Subscribers: 10.7M | Views: 1.5B | Videos: 1.5K
Joined youtube at: 25 August 2014
@gseriesmusic - G Series Music
Subscribers: 11.5M | Views: 3.5B | Videos: 4.2K
Joined youtube at: 16 February 2016
@independenttelevision - Independent Television
Subscribers: 11.7M | Views: 5.5B | Videos: 176.9K
Joined youtube at: 18 August 2011
@ssfoodchallenge - SS FOOD CHALLENGE
Subscribers: 12.7M | Views: 8.4B | Videos: 3.2K
Joined youtube at: 14 March 2021
@ekattortelevision - Ekattor TV
Subscribers: 14.7M | Views: 10.1B | Videos: 153.5K
Joined youtube at: 30 November 2011
@anupammoviesongs - Anupam Movie Songs
Subscribers: 15.0M | Views: 10.6B | Videos: 3.6K
Joined youtube at: 05 February 2018
@channel24digital - Channel 24
Subscribers: 15.4M | Views: 9.3B | Videos: 190.6K
Joined youtube at: 13 June 2016
@farjanadrawingacademy - Farjana Drawing Academy
Subscribers: 15.5M | Views: 4.7B | Videos: 1.8K
Joined youtube at: 15 September 2016
@tonniartandcraft - Tonni art and craft
Subscribers: 19.0M | Views: 9.3B | Videos: 1.8K
Joined youtube at: 21 August 2017
@jamunatvbd - Jamuna TV
Subscribers: 28.6M | Views: 25.1B | Videos: 189.7K
Joined youtube at: 11 December 2017
Thanks for watching!